{
    "id": "e22d1bbdba324ca1b89db3bc5ce72f60",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I look forward ………………… seeing you soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate being shouted …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all anxious …………………… an end to this misunderstanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ................................. poisoning her cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She saved money ................................ giving up coffee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you believe ............................... yourself, you can do anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I think the film is a bit weak ............................ the end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He tripped ................................. the cat and fell downstairs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate the thought ................................ going back to school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She rang me ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you belong ................................... any sports clubs?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents never showed if they were disappointed .............................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}